[{"answer": "Who'd you ask", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You're crazy. She's my friend's girl friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Good morning", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Till noon. This is on my own time.  Hi, Shorty", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Whereabouts", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Want me to run out there", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Bite radius. You know, the size of the mouth", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "The Shark's mouth", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The whale's mouth", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What shark", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "That's it? Probably? Look, sharks are attracted by blood, and thrashing around..", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " Sound", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I got a feeling. I have to act on it", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "We have to do something", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Careful. What's wrong", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Nothing, huh", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Wave to my son", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Maybe nobody will notice. Let's get them back in the bus", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Not bad", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Let's see", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What are you all, blind? It's a shark. Look", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You're damn right that's what it is", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Is that what it is? Dollars? Money? I'll pay for it. Take it out of my salary", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Maybe I don't make as much money as some bullshit ri", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm not sure I can", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Maybe you and my friend could come over to the town beach..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What about sailing", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It'll take us to that place if you're not careful", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Hungry", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " We're going in to eat", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "We're fighting wind and current. I though we'd be out longer, catch the incoming tide", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I was counting on hours", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Negative. I'm still down", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend, I got to switch frequencies, call my boss. We'll meet you over by my friend. Harbor Air out..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Then nothing. If you see him, tell him to switch to an operational frequency, or give me a status report yourself", "docId": "Jaws-2.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "That's what he said", "qsentId": 36}]